(Penny:)Well, do you know anybody?
(Leonard:)Well, I'm sure the guy living with Sheldon
wouldn't mind moving in with you.
(Penny:)Oh, Leonard, honey,
if we started living together...
(Penny:)...I wouldn't be able
to keep my hands off you.
(Penny:)Really?
(Penny:)And you thought my acting lessons
were a waste of money.
Ugh. This moo shu pork's burning a hole
through my duodenum.
Tsk, tsk. Leviticus 11:3.
That which parteth the hoof and cheweth
the cud among the beasts shall ye eat.
Hey, do I mock you with the Bhagavad Gita
every time you scarf down a Whopper?
- Hey, what's going on?
- We're on a quest to the Valley of Fire.
(Howard:)You want the Valley of Fire?
It's right here.